http://www.vinoceros.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
– – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – –
BERKMANN WINE CELLARS LTD
Registered Office 10-12 Brewery Road, London N7 9NH
Registered in England No. 2190816
AWRS Registration No: XXAW00000101932
We can be contacted at the above address or you can email our privacy officer:
Email: privacyofficer@berkmann.co.uk  |  Tel. 020 7609 4711
– – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – –
LIAISON WITH YOU AS REPRESENTATIVE OF A BUSINESS
Where you are acting as a representative of a business with which we trade, we need to process some of your personal data in order to liaise with you in this capacity. For this purpose, we may need to process, your name, job title, business address, email address and phone numbers.
The legal basis we use for this processing is the legitimate interest of ourselves and the business you represent.
We may be provided with this personal information by you or by the business you represent. Alternatively we may obtain it from publicly accessible resources such the web site of the business you represent.
We will retain this personal data for the operational purposes described above until our relationship with the business you represent ceases or until you or the business inform us that you no longer represent it. We may thereafter retain this personal data on extant documents in support of the legitimate interests of ourselves or the business for as long as claims may legally be brought by any of the parties concerned.
INVITING YOU TO EVENTS
In order to organise, advise you of and invite you to events, we need to process some of your personal data. The personal data we process for this purpose is contact details including email address, and dietary preferences.
The legal basis we use for this processing is your prior consent.
You can withdraw consent at any time, and we will then cease to process your personal information for this purpose. Unless you request us not to we will cease to process your personal data for this purpose if you have not attended an event for 24 months.
We may share this personal information with external service providers and organisers for the events you subscribe to and attend.
DIRECT MARKETING
In order to advise you of promotions and product information we need to process some of your personal data. The personal data we process for this purpose is contact details including name, address and, in the case of electronic direct marketing, email address and phone numbers.
The legal basis we use for this processing is your prior consent.
You can withdraw your consent for either electronic direct marketing or non-electronic direct marketing (e.g. by post) or both at any time, and we will then cease to process your personal information for that purpose.
OTHER PURPOSES
We may also process your personal data to comply with our legal obligations, including our legal obligations to you as a data subject.
YOUR RIGHTS
You have the right to be informed of the personal data we hold about you, how we obtain it and what we do with it. Generally, we will provide this information free of charge, however in certain circumstances we reserve the right to charge a reasonable fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you in accordance with UK Data Protection law.
You have the right to request that we correct any of your personal data.
In some circumstances you have the right to request us to erase your personal data.
In some circumstances you have the right to restrict our processing of your personal data.
However while you act as a representative of the business, your exercise of rights 3 and 4 might be limited by your role in the relationship between the business you represent and ourselves. However, should you cease to act as a representative of the business, these rights become fully available to you.
You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data. In particular you have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for direct marketing.
You have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office about our processing of your personal data. The contact points are: Information Commissioner’s Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF; telephone 0303 123 1113; web www.ico.org.uk.
– – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – – –
LIAISON WITH YOU AS AN INDIVIDUAL CUSTOMER
OPENING YOUR ACCOUNT
To create an account for you we need to process some of your personal data, including that required to carry out a credit check.
The legal basis we use for this processing is to enter into a contract with you.
The personal data we process for this purpose is name, address, email address, phone numbers, bank references, bank account details. In order to perform credit checks we use a third-party credit checking service as a Processor on our behalf.
PROCESSING YOUR ORDERS
In order to process your orders, we need to process your personal contact information and payment details.
The legal basis we use for this processing is to perform our contract with you.
The personal data we process for this purpose is name, address, email address, phone numbers, bank account details, payment card details. We may share your delivery information with courier services to deliver your order. We may share your personal data with third parties in support of our legitimate interest in debt recovery.
INVITING YOU TO EVENTS
In order to organise, advise you of and invite you to events, we need to process some of your personal data. The personal data we process for this purpose is contact details including email address, and dietary preferences.
The legal basis we use for this processing is your prior consent.
You can withdraw consent at any time, and we will then cease to process your personal information for this purpose. Unless you request us not to we will cease to process your personal data for these purposes if you have not attended an event for 24 months.
We may share this personal information with external service providers and organisers for the events you subscribe to and attend.
DIRECT MARKETING
In order to advise you of promotions and product information we need to process some of your personal data. The personal data we process for this purpose is contact details including name, address and, in the case of electronic direct marketing, email address and phone numbers.
The legal basis we use for this processing is your prior consent.
You can withdraw your consent for either electronic direct marketing or non-electronic direct marketing (e.g. by post) or both at any time, and we will then cease to process your personal information for that purpose.
OTHER PURPOSES
We may also process your personal data to comply with our legal obligations, including our legal obligations to you as a data subject.
DATA RETENTION
While you have an active account with us we may retain information about your purchasing preferences to facilitate order processing and advise you of product changes.
We will process your personal data for these purposes while you have an active account with us. Thereafter we may retain your personal data where necessary to fulfil our legal obligations.
YOUR RIGHTS
You have the right to be informed of the personal data we hold about you, how we obtain it and what we do with it. Generally, we will provide this information free of charge, however in certain circumstances we reserve the right to charge a reasonable fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you in accordance with UK Data Protection law.
You have the right to request that we correct any of your personal data.
In some circumstances you have the right to request us to erase your personal data.
In some circumstances you have the right to ask us to stop processing your personal data. However, where our processing of your personal data is required to perform a contract with you, we will not be able to perform the contract unless we are able to process that data.
You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data. In particular you have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for direct marketing.
Where we rely on consent, you may withdraw your consent at any time without affecting our provision of any services to you that do not rely on that consent.
You have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office about our processing of your personal data. The contact points are: Information Commissioner’s Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF; telephone 0303 123 1113; web www.ico.org.uk.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
Any changes we make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on our website, and, notified to you by e-mail.
